Guide to the Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013.
Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013
- Series I. Articles Submitted for Publication in RRPE
  - Subseries B: Numbered Articles Submitted And Accepted, (originally submitted to specific RRPE issues)
    - #1483b- Reviewed by Dymski, Gary. "Capitalism, Socialism, and Post-Keynesianism", 1996 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - #1485b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Institutional Economics and the Theory of Social Value", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - #1488 - Kirshner, Jonathan "Disinflation, Structural Change, and Distribution", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - #1498b - Reviewed by Merrett, Chris. "Radical Political Economy and Reformulation", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - #1500b - Reviewed by Conroy, Paul. "A Japanese Approach to Political Economy: Unoist Variations", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - #1504a - Palley, Tom. "The Academic Jungle: Social Practice and the Survival of Economic Ideas", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - #1509a - Burkett, Paul. "Insider/Outside Approach to Unemployment", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - #1514a - Green, David. "Pensions, Class and Capital: An International Perspective", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - 1515a - Sinha, Ajit. "The Transformation Problem: A Critique of the New Solution", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - #1517b - Reviewed by Llorente, Renzo. "Self-Ownership, Freedom, and Equality", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - #1521a - Grabel, Ilene. "Creating Credible Economic Policy in Developing and Transitional Economies", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - #1525a - Campbell, Al. "The Transformation Problem: A Simple Presentation of the New Solution", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - #1527a - Lippit, Victor. "Market Socialism in China?", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - #1528a - Lippit, Victor. "The Reconstruction of a Social Structure of Accumulation in the United States", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - 1529a - Nilsson, Eric. "Wage Dependence in the Postwar United States", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - #1530a - Kliman, Andrew. "The Okishio Theorem: An Obituary", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - #1531a - Johnson, Mark. "Power in a Historically Contingent Analysis of Capitalism", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - #1532a - Reich, Michael. "Social Structure of Accumulation Theory: Retrospect and Prospect", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - #1534S - Hammond, John. "Popular Education in El Salvador: Lessons for College Teachers", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - #1536a - Gunn, Christopher. "The Nonprofit Sector: Radical Potential?", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - #1539b - Reviewed by Lee, Frederic. "Post-Keynesian Economic Theory", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - #1541b - Reviewed by Gandy, D. Ross. "America's New Economic Order", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - #1562 - Naples, Michele. "The Volume, Frequency, and Size of Business Failures: A Social Structure of Accumulation Approach", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - #1572b - Reviewed by Devine, James. "The Economics of the Profit Rate: Competition, Crises and Historical Tendencies in Capitalism", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - #1590b - Senick-Goldstein, Jennifer. "Kremlin Capitalism: Privatizing the Russian Economy", 1997 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - #1594 - Davanzati, Guglielmo Forges. "Wages Fund, High Wages and Social Conflict in a Classical Model of Unemployment Equilibrium", 2001 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - #1606 - Kadri, Ali. "Oscillating Labour from the West Bank", 1998 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - #1631 - Mavroudeas, Stavros. "The Role of Consumption in the theory of Regulation", 2002 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - #1719 - Zafirovski, Milan. "Measuring and Making Sense of Labor Exploitation in Contemporary Capitalism", 2002 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - #1724 - Thompson, Frank. "Golden Age vs. Golden Rule: Capitalists vs. Workers in Growth Theory", 2001 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - #1755 - Robinson, Warren. "Capitalism, Family Structure and the Declining Value of Procreation in the Developing World", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - #1773 - Ross, Eric. "Malthusianism, Capitalist Agriculture and the Fate of Peasants in the Modern World Food System", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - #1785 - Dumenil, Gerard; Levy, Dominique. "The Field of Capital Mobility and the Gravitation of Profit Rates (USA 1948-1997)", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - #1786 - Dumenil, Gerard; Levy, Dominique. "The Profit Rate: Where and How Much Did It Fall? Did It Recover? (1948-1997)", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - #1818b - Reviewed by Lemus-Ruiz, Blanca. "The Point of Production: Work Environment in Advanced Industrial Societies", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - #1830 - O'Hara, Phillip. "Deep Recession and Financial Instability or a New Long Wave of Economic Growth for US Capitalism?", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - #1839b - Reviewed by Bechtold,Brigitte. "Recent Developments in Economic Methodology", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - #1847b - Reviewed by Rein, Sandra. "Globalization and the Dilemmas of the State in the South", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - #1852b - Reviewed by Orhangazi, Ozgur. "Class Warfare in the Information Age", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - #1855 - Wilson, Tamar Diana. "Forms of Male Domination and Female Subordination: Homeworkers vs. Maquiladora Workers in Mexico", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - #1857b - Reviewed by Wood, Geoffrey. "The Institutional Basis for Economic and Social Progress - Perspectives and Policies", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - #1864 - Pisani, Michael. "The Negative Impact of Structural Adjustment on Sectoral Earnings in Nicaragua", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - #1866b - Reviewed by Ortiz, Etelberto. "Polarizing Mexico: The Impact of Liberalization Strategy", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - #1867P - Jacques, Peter. "Wal-Mart or World-Mart? A Teaching Case Study", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - #1871b - Reviewed by Diskin, Jonathan. "Global Economy, Global Justice: Theoretical Objections and Policy Alternatives to Neoliberalism", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - #1872 - Fayazmanesh, Sassan. "The Politics of the US Economic Sanctions Against Iran", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - #1874b - Reviewed by De Angelis, Massimo. "The Limits of Capital", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - #1875b - Reviewed by Rao, D. Tripati. "Managing Economics", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - #1881b - Reviewed by Webber, Jeffery. "Political Power and Social Theory", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - #1883 - Cato, Molly Scott. "Employment Policy in Rhondda-Cynon-Taff as Judged by its Targets", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - #1884b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "The State in Modern Society", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - #1885b - Reviewed by Sinha, Ajit. "Value, Distribution and Capital Essays in Honour of Pierangelo Gareganani", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - #1890 - Harms, John. "The New Economy: What's New - What's Not", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - #1891b - Reviewed by Brennan, David. "The Rise of Fiduciary Capitalism: How Institutional Investors Can Make Corporate America More Democratic", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - #1892b - Reviewed by Thompson, Michael. "The Political Economy of Uneven Development: The Case of China", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - #1893b - Reviewed by Cohen, Philip. "Glass Ceilings and Asian Americans", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - #1894b - Reviewed by Pisani, Michael. "Repression, Resistance, and Democratic Transition in Central America", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - #1895b - Reviewed by Dimand, Robert. "Life and Work of Karl Polanyi and Karl Polanyi in Vienna", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - #1896b - Reviewed by Salah, Georgina. "The Politics of the Asian Economic Crisis", 2001 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - #1897b - Reviewed by Christensen, Kimberly. "The Invisible Heart: Economics and Family Values", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - #1899 - Subasat, Turan. "What Does the Heckscher-Ohlin Model Contribute to International Trade Theory?", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - #1904b - Reviewed by Huffman, Matt. "Impacts of Affirmative Action: Policies and Consequences in California", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - #1905b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Political Economy and Contemporary Capitalism", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - #1907 - Lavoie, Marc. "Real Wages and Unemployment with Effective and Notional Demand for Labor", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - #1910b - Fuller, Elaine. "US Economic Development Policies Towards the Pacific Rim", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - #1911b - Reviewed by Orhangazi, Ozgur. "Global Instability, The Political Economy of World Economic Governance", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - #1916b - Reviewed by Dowd, Doug. "How the Clinton Administration Completed the Reagan Revolution", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - #1920b - Reviewed by Tamayo, Pedro. "Dying for Growth: Global Inequality and the Health of the Poor", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - #1924b - Reviewed by Tilly, Chris. "Who Gets the Good Jobs? Combating Race and Gender Disparities"bs?, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - #1926b - Reviewed by Barkin, David. "Toxic Exports: The Transfer of Hazardous Wastes from Rich to Poor Countries", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - #1930b - Reviewed by Reuss, Alejandro. "Development as Freedom", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - #1933 - Oncu, Ahmet. "Wither Business Ideology: Revisiting Veblen's Theory of Engineers as Revolutionary Actors", 2008 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - #1935b - Reviewed by Laibman, David. "Debunking Economics", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - #1936b - Reviewed by Willoughby, John. "The Labor of Development: Workers and the Transformation of Capitalism in Kerala, India", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - #1938b - Reviewed by Nayeri, Kamran. "Review of Market Socialism: The Debate Among Socialists", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - #1942b - Reviewed by Wilson, Tamar Diana. "Sweatshop Warriors: Immigrant Women Workers Take on the Global Factory", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - #1943b - Reviewed by Burkett, Paul. "The Value of Marx: Political Economy for Contemporary Capitalism", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - #1949b - Reviewed by Wilson, Tamar Diana. "Disposable Domestics", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - #1959b - Reviewed by Tabrizi, Behrouz. "The Working Class Majority: America"s Best Kept Secret", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - #1960b - Reviewed by Veneziani, Roberto. "Recasting Egalitarianism: New Rules for Communities, States and Markets", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - #1961b - Reviewed by Boyce, James. "The Ghost of Malthus:, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - #1963b - Reviewed by Kenner, Martin. "The Monied Metropolis: New York City and the Consolidation of the American Bourgeoisie", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - #1969b - Cerni, Paula. "Global Shift: Transforming the World Economy", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - #1970b - Reviewed by Sacouman, R. James. "The Atlantic Economy: Britain, the US and Ireland", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - #1976b - Reviewed by Saad-Filho, Alfredo. "Transcending the Economy: On the Potential of Passionate Labour and the Wastes of the Market", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - #1984b - Reviewed by Nader, John. "The Invention of Capitalism", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - #1988b - Reviewed by de Kadt, Maarten. "Money Makes the World Go Around", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - #1994b - Reviewed by Duchesne, Ricardo. "Malthus and the Demographic Sustems of Modern Europe and Imperial China", 2003 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - #1996b - Reviewed by Laibman, David. "Toward an Unknown Marx", 2002 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - #2014 - Hosseini, Hamid. "From Communist Manifesto to Empire: How Have Marxists Viewed Global Capitalism in History", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - #2019 - Herrera, Remy. "The Hidden Face of Endogenous Growth Theory", 2004 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - #2041 - Kettell,Steve. "Circuits of Capital and Overproduction: A Marxist Analysis of the Present World Economic Crisis", 2004 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - #2049 - Sherman, Howard. "The Making of Radical Economists", 2004 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - #2060 - Lauer, Helen. "Shifting the Blame: How Tradition vs. Modernity Dualism Contributes to the HIV/AIDS Crisis' in Africa, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - #2065 - Nesvetailova, Anastasia. "Fictitious Capital, Real Debts", 2004 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - #2075 - Hahnel, Robin. "Exploitation: A Modern Approach, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - #2081 - Milonakis, Dimitris; Fine, Ben. "Douglass North's Remaking of Economic History: A Marxist Critique", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - #2083b - Reviewed by Romero, Sergio. "Lost Ground: Welfare Reform,Poverty and Beyond:, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - #2084 - Taskalotos, Euclid. "Social Conflict and the Effectiveness of Aggregate Demand Management Policies", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - #2103 - Yeldan, Erinc. "Turkey in 2005 and Beyond: Macroeconomic Policy, Patterns of Growth and Persistent Fragilities" (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - #2105 - Baiman, Ron. "Unequal Exchange Without the Labor Theory of Value: Need for Global Marshall Plan and Solidarity Trading Regime", 2004 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - #2109 - Ozel, Huseyin. "The Notion of Power and the Metaphysics of Labor Values", 2007 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - #2110 - Venida, Victor. "Marxian Categories Empirically Estimated: The Philippines 1961-1964", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - #2113 - Thompson, Noel. "Socialist Political Economies and the Growth of Mass Consumption in Britain and the United States, 1880-1914", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - #2115 - Migone, Andrea. "Hedonistic Consumerism: Patterns of Consumption in Modern Capitalism", 2006 (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - #2116 - Mavroudeas, Stavros. "The History of Political Economy and Post-Modernism", 2006 (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - #2119 - Redmond, William. "Home Equity, Fungibility and Consumption: The Increasing Rationalization of Society", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - #2122 - Vernengo, Matias. "Technology, Finance and Dependency: Latin American Radical Political Economy in Retrospect", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - #2124 - Feliz, Mariano. "A Note on Argentina, Its Crisis and the Theory of Exchange Rate Determination", 2005 (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - #2127 - Starr, Martha. "Saving, Spending and Self-Control: Cognition versus Consumer Culture", 2004 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - #2130 - Rieu, Dong-Min. "A Re-examination of the Quantitative Issues in the New Interpretation", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - #2132b - Reviewed by Maier, Mark. "The Real World in the Classroom: A Review of Dollars and Sense Anthologies", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - #2133b - Reviewed by Sandronsky, Seth. "Naming the System: Inequality and Work in the Global Economy", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - #2135 - Pietrykowski, Bruce. "Exploring New Directions for Research in the Radical Political Economy of Consumption", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - #2134b - Reviewed by Brownlow, Graham. "When Histories Collide: The Development and Impact of Individualistic Capitalism", 2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - #2136b - Reviewed by Ruwanpuna, Kanchana. "Post-Conlonialism Meets Economics", 2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - #2137b - Reviewed by Webber, Jeffery. "Imperialism Without Colonies", 2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - #2139 - Preparata, Guido Giacomo. "Perishable Money in a Threefold Commonwealth", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - #2141b - Reviewed by Nesiba, Reynold. "Debunking Economics: The Naked Emperor of the Social Sciences", 2995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - #2143 - Goldstein, Jonathan. "Marxian Microfoundations: Contribution or Detour?", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - #2147 - Tarrit, Fabien. "A brief History, Scope and Peculiarities of Analytical Marxism", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - #2149b - Reviewed by Williams, Michael. "Dance of the Dialectic: Steps in Marx's Method", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - #2150b - Reviewed by Brownlow, Graham. "Evolutionary Economics: Program and Scope", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - #2154b - Reviewed by Stilwell, Frank. "The Struggle for Political Economy at the University of Sydney", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - #2154b - Reviewed by Goldin, Jaqui. "Visions of Development: A Study of Human Values", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - #2155 - Izquierdo, Sergio Camara. "The Dynamics of the Profit Rate in Spain", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - #2160 - Vetter, Henrik. "Golden Age and Golden Rule in Unionised Economies", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - #2163 - Cipolla, Francisco Paulo. "The Concept of Market Value: A Critical Note on Itoh's Theory", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - #2164b - Reviewed by Chandra, Pratyush. "The Politics of Europe: Monetary Union and Class", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - #2166b - Reviewed by Kennedy, Marie. "Democracy in Action: Community Organizing and Urban Change", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - #2167 - Nakhaie, M. Reza; Smylie, Lisa; Arnold, Robert. "Social Inequalities, Social Capital and Health of Canadians", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - #2168b - Reviewed by Mahoney, Joseph. "Basic Economics" and "Applied Economics", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - #2170b - Reviewed by Farrant, Andrew. "Radical Political Economy", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - #2172b - Reviewed by Johnson, William. "Unfair Advantage: Workers Freedom of Association in the United States", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - #2173b - Reviewed by Peters, John. "Reclaiming Evolution", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - #2176b - Reviewed by Webber, Jeffery. "To Inherit the Earth: The Landless Movement and the Struggle for Brazil", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - #2178b - Reviewed by Wood, Geoffrey. "Continuity and Change in Structures and Social Life", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - #2179b - Reviewed by Scott, Robert. "Banker to the Poor: Micro-Lending and the Battle Against World Poverty", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - #2183b - Reviewed by Kaboub, Fadhel. "Marx, Veblen, and Contemporary Institutional Political Economy", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - #2184b - Reviewed by Bendien, Jurriaan. "Reinventing Functional Finance; Transformational Growth and Full Employment", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - #2186 - Ellerman, David. "The Role of Capital in Capitalist and in Labor-Managed Firms", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - #2190 - Murphy, Jonathan. "Another White Wash? A Small Quibble with Fred Lee's History of American Radical Economics", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - #2195b - Reviewed by Kumar, Hari. "NHS plc - The Privatisation of Our Health Care", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - #2198b - Reviewed by Schuftan, Claudio. "Dignity Counts: A Guide to Using Budget Analysis to Advance Human Rights", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - #2200b - Reviewed by King, Mary. "Growing Public: Social Spending and Economic Growth Since the Eighteenth Century", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - #2201 - Herrick, Clare. "The Southern African Famine and Genetically Modified Food Aid", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - #2202b - Reviewed by Kuecker, Glen David. "When Corporations Rule the World", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - #2205b - Reviewed by Cerni, Paula. "After the Empire: The Breakdown of the American Order", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - #2009b - Reviewed by Ho, Tsung-Wu. "Who Owns America?", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - #2210b - Reviewed by Dowd, Douglas. "China's New Order: Society, Politics, and Economy in Transition", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - #2211b - Reviewed by Zamora, Daniel Tagle. "Duncan K. Foley, Unholy Trinity: Labor, Capital, and Land in the New Economy", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - #2212b - Reviewed by Farrant, Andrew. "Microeconomics: Behavior, Institutions, and Evolution", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - #2215b - REviewed by Larudee, Mehrene. "Inside Stories", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - #2216b - Reviewed by Bechtold, Brigitte. "Feminist Post-Development Thought", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - #2217b - Reviewed by Coyle, Eugene. "Tuxedo Park", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - #2218b - Reviewed by Thompson, Frank. "Understanding Capitalism: Competition, Command and Change", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - #2219 - Abdel-Haleim, Sahar Mohamed; Salevurakis, John William. "Bread Subsidies in Egypt", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - #2220 - Hudson, Mark. "With Friends Like These: The Corporate Response to Fair Trade Coffee", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - #2221b - Reviewed by Gasper, Des. "Crossing the Mainstream - Ethical and Methodological Issues in Economics", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - #2223b - Reviewed by Elardo, Justin. "After the New Economy", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - #Reviewed by Cohen, Philip. "Confronting Economic Gender Inequality", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - #2225b - Reviewed by Burczak, Theodore. "Postmodernism, Economics and Knowledge", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - #2227 - Lavoie, Marc. "Capacity Utilization, Inflation and Monetary Policy", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - #2228b - Reviewed by Flynn, Matthew. "A Theory of Global Capitalism", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - #2229 - Saros, Daniel. "The Turnover Continuum: A Marxist Analysis of Capitalist Fluctuations", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - #2231b - Reviewed by Liang, Yan. "Growth, Distribution and Effective Demand", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - #2233 - McDonough, Terrence. "Social Structures of Accumulation Theory: The State of the Art", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - #2234b - Reviewed by Chattopadhyay, Paresh. "Marx on Suicide", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - #2235b - Reviewed by Lippit, Victor. "Taxation Without Representation in Contemporary Rural China", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - #2238 - McDermott, John. "Future Time in Microeconomics", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - #2239b - Reviewed by Thompson, Frank. "The Politics of the Internet in Third World Development", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - #2240b - Reviewed by Clement, Roland. "Shrimp Farming and Mangrove Loss in Thailand", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - #2242b - Reviewed by Toporowski, Jan. "Social Foundations of Markets, Money and Credit", 2005 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - #2246b - Reviewed by Spronk, Susan. "The Politics of Water Privatization in the Third World", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - #2248b - Reviewed by Vernengo, Matias. "New Thinking in Macroeconomics: Social, Institutional, and Environmental Perspectives", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - #2249b - Reviewed by Bair, Asatar. "African Americans in the U.S. Economy", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - #2250 - Moseley, Fred. "The Macro-Monetary Interpretation of Marx's Theory", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - #2251b - Reviewed by Nayeri, Kamran. "Perspectives on Socialist Development in Cuba", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - #2255b - Reviewed by Brownlow, Graham. "The Evolution of Institutional Economics", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - #2257 - Brennan, David. "Deconstructing Share Repurchases", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - #2258 - Wood, Phillip. "Cultivating Voters: The Social Relations of Agriculture and Racial Politics in the New South", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - #2260b - Reviewed by Ruwanpura, Kanchana. "Fragments of Development: Nation, Gender, and the Space of Modernity", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - #2264 - Parker, Martin. "Co-operatives, Labour and the State: The English Labour Economists Revisited", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - #2265 - Aguliar-Conraria, Luis. "A Note on the Stability Properties of Goodwin's Predator-Prey Model", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - #2268b - Reviewed by Duggan, Marie. "Capital Resurgent: Roots of the Neoliberal Revolution", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - #2269b - Reviewed by Caterino, Brian. "Correcting Rights", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - #2273b - Reviewed by Hahnel, Robin. "Third Sector Development: Making Up for the Market", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - #2274b - Reviewed by Martinez, Hepzibah Munoz. "The Political Economy of Exchange Rate Policy-Making", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - #2276b - Reviewed by Leitch, Richard. "The Making of a Cybertariat Ursula Uuws", 2006 (Box 22, Folder 80)